<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<help>
	<login>
		<createinitialaccount>
			<createsuperuser>
			<des>When you set up a Hyperfiler, you create a super administrator account. The super administrator account lets you configure the Hyperfiler and create more administrator users. 
			</des>
			<des>Provide a user name, password, and email account for the super administrator.	Passwords should be at least 8 characters and should not contain spaces.	
			</des>		
		</createsuperuser>
		<userlogin><des>Enter a valid user name and password to log in. After three failed attempts your account will be temporarily locked.</des>
		</userlogin> 
			<email>
				<des>The email must be less then 64 characters in length.</des>
			</email>
			<username>
				<des>Only letters [a-z, A-Z], numbers, periods and @ are valid characters.The username must be 3 to 32 characters in length.</des>
			</username>
			<password>
				<des>The password must contain at least eight characters and include a minimum of one capital letter, one lowercase letter and a number digit.
			</des>
			</password>
		</createinitialaccount>
	</login>
	
	<configuration>
		<generalsettings>
			<basedon>
				<des>The default setting is New Coniguration.drop-down menu offers the existing Hyperfilers in the system as models, and offers two                     more options:
				</des>
				<des>
					 View all saved configs
  			   </des>
			   <des>
					 Import Config. File
			   </des>
			</basedon>
			
			<abbreviation>
				<des>For each Hyperfiler the user must enter an abbreviation.</des>
			</abbreviation>
			
			<encryption>
				<des>Here the user sets whether then want encryption on the wire for the Hyperfiler.'No' selected by default. <a href=  		"http://www.peaxy.com/help/xxx.html">here learn more.</a></des>
				<des></des>
			</encryption>
		</generalsettings>
		
		<storageclass>
			<des></des>
			<basedon>
				<des></des>
				<des></des>
			</basedon>
			<cloudstorage>
				<des></des>
			</cloudstorage>
			<drivetype>
				<des></des>
			</drivetype>
			<usablestoragespace>
				<des></des>
				<des></des>
			</usablestoragespace>
		</storageclass>
	</configuration>
	
	
	<license>
		<licensereviewinfo>
			<licensetype>
				<des>Tooltip info for license type, to be entered.</des>
			</licensetype>
			<dataspace>
				<des>Tooltip info for data space capacity level, to be entered.</des>
			</dataspace>
			<supportlevel>
				<des>Tooltip info for support level, to be entered.</des>
			</supportlevel>
			<additionalfeatures>
				<des>Tooltip info for additional features, to be entered.</des>
			</additionalfeatures>
		</licensereviewinfo>
	</license>
</help>